Then I think there's a reasonable thing that you can think, which is
Should you stay on that project or should you go?
If you spot that a project has got so many different
wild and scary bets that it's got no chance of succeeding at all
What should you do about that? Should you stay? Or should you go? And I think it's legitimate in those kinds of situations. Again, this is something that I've tried to like
take have a different take on kind of a lot of project management books.
Is
That not all projects succeed. That's one of the kind of important aspects of looking at projects in terms of bets. And so if you do look at
projects in terms of bets, you realize that some projects are going to fail. And
Some of the people who are associated with that project are going to be exercising their right to play heads I win, tails you lose, and be around when the project succeeds and not around when the project fails. And there's no reason why you can't do the same
There's no reason why you can't think, well, this project's not going to work out. So you can go somewhere else.